at this point we've looked at a lot of
在这一点上 我们已经查看了很多
brushes between all of the default
在所有默认的
brushes in CR the brushes that I've
把我的画笔刷进CR
created the brushes other artists have
创作了其他艺术家的画笔
created and the brushes that you can
所创建的画笔和画笔
create there are more brushes available
创建有更多笔刷可用
than you could ever use in one lifetime
比你一生都用不到的
for a first-time user of Crea the sheer
对于Crea的第一次用户来说 这是纯粹的
number of brushes to choose from can
可供选择的笔刷数量
feel intimidating through
在整个过程中感到害怕
experimentation you will discover which
通过实验 您会发现
brushes are valuable to you but I will
画笔对你很有价值 但我会的
also offer some suggestions for brushes
我还提供了一些关于画笔的建议
that I find useful I would consider
我觉得有用的 我会认为
these to be my Essential brushes to make
这些都是我制作的必备画笔
them quicker to access all of these
他们可以更快地访问所有这些
brushes are located in a custom bundle
画笔位于自定义捆绑包中
before we begin I'll remind you to reset
在我们开始之前 我要提醒您重新设置
any modified brushes to their defaults
将任何修改后的画笔恢复为其默认设置
to ensure they match my
以确保它们与我的
demonstrations I'll use the brush
演示我会用刷子
testing template to demonstrate let's
测试模板来演示 让我们
start with some airbrushes in the
开始时使用一些喷枪
rendering AR category the first variant
将AR类别呈现为第一个变体
is called airbrush soft airbrushes are
被称为喷枪软喷笔是
one of the oldest and most basic brushes
最古老、最基本的画笔之一
one can use to create digital art but
人们可以用来创作数字艺术 但
they are still incredibly useful The
它们仍然是非常有用的
Feathered edges and slowly building
羽毛般的边缘和缓慢的建筑
opacity make your brushes perfect for
不透明使您的画笔完美地
adding form to objects and creating hand
为对象添加形状并创建手
painted gradients I have a lot of
我有很多绘制的渐变
control over the brush opacity using pen
使用钢笔控制画笔的不透明度
pressure you can also apply blending
压力你也可以应用混合
modes to modify how the brush media
修改画笔媒体方式的模式
blends with underlying paint you can
与底层油漆混合 您可以
quickly access these from the properties
从酒店快速访问这些内容
bar let's set it to multiply if I
让我们将其设置为乘法 如果我
overlap Strokes I can build up my color
重叠的笔触我可以增加我的颜色
darker without having to change anything
更暗 不需要改变任何东西
in the color selector when working with
在使用时在颜色选择器中
blending modes you may also want to
混合模式您可能还想要
blend Strokes with underlying colors
将笔触与底层颜色混合
using an appropriate layer blending mode
使用适当的层混合模式
I'll revert the template the grainy
我会将模板还原为颗粒状
airbrush is similar to the previous
喷枪类似于以前的
airbrush but with the ability to use
喷枪 但有能力使用
texture you can see that it has a soft
质地你可以看到它有一种柔软的
edge with some texture throughout the
整个边缘都有一些纹理
stroke I can easily change this from the
笔划我可以很容易地从
properties bar glazing airbrush is also
物业吧玻璃喷枪也是
similar to the soft air brush but it
类似于柔软的空气刷 但它
uses wash instead of buildup for the
使用洗涤 而不是堆积
paint blending mode have a look at the
画图混合模式请查看
previous lesson to learn about the
上一课要了解的
differences between wash and buildup
洗涤和堆积的区别
this brush is useful for slowly building
此笔刷对于缓慢构建非常有用
up thin glazes of paint with opacity
上一层不透明的薄釉
that is more even and easy to control
这更均匀 也更容易控制
next is the glow airbrush which also has
接下来是辉光喷枪 它也有
airbrush qualities this variant builds
这个变种制造的喷枪特性
up colors in a way that mimics natural
以一种模仿自然的方式提升色彩
light the blending moon is set to screen
点亮交融的月亮被设置为屏幕
but you can also get some nice lighting
但是你也可以得到一些很好的照明
effects using the color Dodge Mode I use
我使用的颜色减淡模式的效果
this brush a lot for lighting objects
这把刷子非常适合照明物体
and
和
backgrounds next is the pepper air brush
背景下一步是胡椒气刷
this brush sprays out droplets of paint
这把刷子会喷出几滴油漆
that vary in size at only a few pixels
它们的大小只有几个像素
in diameter this brush works well for
这把刷子的直径适用于
creating Stars snow and sand you may
创造星星 雪和沙子 你可以
want to use the mouse to make single
想用鼠标做单人吗？
dabs so you don't build up too many
轻拍 这样你就不会积累太多
features at once the size of the
的大小立即显示为
features can be controlled in the brush
可以在画笔中控制要素
editor under spray shape you will need
喷雾形状下的编辑器您将需要
to link the width and height to keep the
链接宽度和高度以保持
features round unlinking will allow you
要素轮换取消链接将允许您
to make ellipses and lines the pixel
使椭圆和线条成为像素的步骤
airbrush is next this brush sprays out
喷枪是下一个喷出的喷枪
even finer Speckles you can use this for
更细小的斑点 你可以用它来
a more controlled spray that builds up
一种更受控制的喷雾
slowly moving on to some other brush
慢慢地移到其他的画笔上
types we have the smooth pen this
类型我们有流畅的笔这
creates an opaque stroke with a smooth
创建具有平滑效果的不透明笔触
edge it works well for inking or
边缘它适用于墨水或
blocking in layers you could use this
在层中分块你可以用这个
brush to establish the silhouette of an
用刷子勾勒出一幅
object and then use other types of
对象 然后使用其他类型的
brushes to add form to it you can edit
画笔可向其添加可编辑的表单
the brush tip to tweak the edges of this
笔刷提示调整此对象的边缘
brush if you want the edges of your
如果您想要刷牙边缘 请使用刷子
silhouette to be sharper or
轮廓更清晰或更清晰
softer let's move on to the sketching
柔和一点 让我们继续画素描
pencil this is a fantastic pencil
这是一支很棒的铅笔
because you can tilt your pen to change
因为你可以倾斜你的笔来改变
the shape and opacity of the dab
涂抹的形状和不透明度
allowing you to emulate shading with the
允许您使用
side of it opacity and texture both
它的侧面不透明和纹理都
respond nicely to pen pressure as you
很好地应对笔压 因为你
can see I can create a smooth gradient
可以看到我可以创建一个平滑的渐变
from dark to light by modulating my
从黑暗到光明通过调节我的
pressure this is my go-to brush for
压力 这是我的首选刷牙
sketching and pencil drawing because it
素描和铅笔画 因为它
has a superb look and feel the cylinder
具有极佳的外观和感觉的圆柱体
pen is an rgba type brush that uses a
PEN是一种RGBA型画笔 它使用
lightness map to create a 2.5d stroke
创建2.5D笔划的亮度贴图
I'll select a dark brown and you can see
我会选择深棕色的 你可以看到
that I'm able to use varied pressure to
我可以用不同的压力
paint tree branches that look almost
把树枝涂得看起来像是
three dimension itional this may save
三维关系这可以省去
you from having to add shading later
您不必在以后添加阴影
with an airbrush you can even use it for
有了喷枪 你甚至可以用它来
leaves if you make shorter strokes this
如果你用更短的笔划 就会离开
brush could even be useful for creating
画笔甚至可以用于创建
textures as you can see if I place
纹理 你可以看到 如果我放置
Strokes right up against each other now
现在击球要靠在一起了
let's check out the chalk which I find
让我们看看我找到的粉笔
useful for adding texture to objects you
对于为对象添加纹理非常有用
can get a lot of different looks from
可以得到许多不同的外观从
many of my brushes by changing your
我的许多画笔都是通过改变你的
texture for a texture that is even more
纹理的纹理更是
random there is random chalk this brush
这把刷子上有乱画的粉笔
has a bit more randomization to make the
具有更多的随机性 以使
texture less repetive itive you can see
纹理不那么重复 你可以看到
the difference if I compare two strokes
如果我比较两个笔划会有什么不同
both of these brushes can benefit from
这两种刷子都可以受益于
setting the paint blending to screen or
将油漆混合设置为屏幕或
multiply as you can see I can use a
乘法 如您所见 我可以使用
single color to create the base color of
要创建其基色的单一颜色
foliage as well as the highlights and
树叶以及亮点和
shadows chalk is just a name for these
阴影粉笔只是这些的一个名字
brushes I use them more for their shape
刷子我更多地用它们来做形状
than their
比他们的
medium next is sponge this brush has a
中号 然后是海绵 这个刷子有一个
spongy dab with a lot of detail you can
海绵轻拍 有很多细节 你可以
dab with this brush or overlap Strokes
用此笔刷或重叠笔触轻拍
to create a more intricate texture
创建更复杂的纹理
texture if we make our brush bigger the
纹理如果我们使画笔更大
texture gets larger if we make the brush
如果我们制作画笔 纹理会变得更大
smaller the texture gets finer you can
质地越小越好
also modify the texture pattern this
还可以修改纹理图案
brush works well to add a quick texture
笔刷可以很好地添加快速纹理
overlay on a separate
覆盖在单独的
layer variable shape uses a mast brush
图层可变形状使用主画笔
tip to blend between two different dab
调和两种不同面团的小贴士
shapes making the brush larger increases
使画笔变大的形状会增加
the size of the shapes heavy pressure
形状的大小重压
makes distinct shapes that are more
使不同的形状更具
opaque and light pressure makes soft
不透明和轻微的压力会使人变软
shapes that are more transparent I find
我发现更透明的形状
this brush to be incredibly useful for
这把刷子非常有用
painting foliage because it generates a
绘制树叶 因为它会生成一个
wide variety of leaf patterns and by
种类繁多的树叶图案和
modifying the texture pattern I can
修改纹理图案我可以
randomize the leaf shapes even
均匀地随机化树叶形状
more next I'll load the blenders
更多下一步我要装入搅拌机
template and let's take a look at some
模板 让我们来看看一些
of my Essential blenders as you can see
如你所见 我的基本搅拌机
it's possible to get a lot of different
有可能会有很多不同的
looks out of the blenders but I only use
从搅拌机里往外看 但我只用
a handful of these variants on a regular
几个这样的变种在常规的
basis one blender that is very useful is
一种非常有用的搅拌机是
the diffuse blender using very light
使用非常轻的漫反射搅拌器
pressure allows you to slightly fuzz up
压力可以让你稍微变得模糊起来
the pixels heavy pressure really
像素压力真的很大
scatters them this brush works well for
分散它们这把刷子很管用
blending colors together with a drier
用烘干机将颜色混合在一起
appearance grainy blender has a similar
外观颗粒状的搅拌机有类似的
effect though the scattering is more
虽然散射更多 但效果
pronounced due to the texture being used
由于所使用的纹理而发音
you can modify the pattern to get
您可以修改模式以获得
different
不同
textures let's try another brush called
纹理让我们试一试另一种画笔
water blender this blender emulates
这台搅拌机模仿的水搅拌机
blending transparent media with plain
将透明媒体与普通媒体混合
water the edges of the brush are soft
浇水：刷子的边缘很软
which gives the blend a wet
这给了混合物一种湿的
appearance another useful blender is
外观另一个有用的搅拌机是
blur I can use it to soften the edges of
模糊我可以用它来柔化边缘
objects to make them out of focus
对象以使它们变得模糊
lowering the opacity makes the blurring
降低不透明度会使模糊
more subtle this brush works well to add
更微妙 这把刷子可以很好地添加
depth and distance to your seene next is
深度和距离下一步是
oily blender this is an oily looking
油腻的搅拌机这是一款油腻的
blender that can also smudge around the
搅拌机 也可以涂抹周围的
paint tilting your pen changes the angle
画笔倾斜会改变角度
of the dab giving you more
会给你带来更多
randomization next up is coarse oily
随机化的下一个是粗糙的油性
blender this blender is similar to oily
搅拌机这种搅拌机类似于油性的
blender but with a sharper more streaky
搅拌机 但有更锋利的条纹
smudging also included with the blenders
搅拌机中还包括污渍
are some Distortion brushes these are
是一些扭曲笔刷吗这些是
not technically blenders but they can
技术上不是搅拌机 但他们可以
mix up paint which borders on blending
混合近乎混合的油漆
for example I can use distort push to
例如 我可以使用扭曲推送来
mix the paint together which gives the
把油漆混合在一起 这样就可以
impression of blending if I mix for long
如果我长时间地混合 就会有混合的感觉
enough I will eventually create
我最终会创造足够的
intermediate colors we'll come back to
我们将回到中间颜色
Distortion brushes in a later
稍后会出现失真
lesson let's explore the variance in my
让我们来探索一下我的
pallet knives category I'll return to
我将返回托盘刀具类别
the brush testing template flat knife is
所述刷检模板平刀
an excellent brush because it can add
一把很棒的刷子 因为它可以添加
paint and smudge at the same time if you
同时涂抹和涂抹 如果您
use heavy pressure you will apply paint
使用沉重的压力 你会涂上油漆
if you lighten your pressure the brush
如果你减轻刷子的压力
runs out of paint and begins to smudge
油漆用完了 开始弄脏
the underlying colors returning to heavy
底层的色彩回归了浓重
pressure adds paint again I love the way
压力又一次增加了油漆 我喜欢这种方式
I can lay down paint and then blend it
我可以放下油漆 然后把它调和起来
out it feels very natural as you can see
在外面 你可以看到 它感觉非常自然
I can create water Ripples and easily
我可以轻而易举地创造出水波
give them form many of these pallet
给他们许多这样的托盘
knives are flat so they can be rotated
刀子是平的 所以可以旋转
using tilt being able to rotate a flat
使用倾斜可以旋转平板
dab allows you to intuitively change the
DAB允许您直观地更改
shape of your marks to get a wide range
你的分数的形状可以得到一个很大的范围
of effects from tree trunks to
从树干到树干
foliage let's try the Mountain Knife
让我们试试山刀吧
next this is a great brush for painting
其次 这是一支很棒的画笔
silhouettes of mountains that fade into
逐渐淡出的山脉的剪影
mist lighter pressure will toggle to
喷雾打火机压力将切换到
mixing so you can smudge the paint the
混合 这样你就可以涂抹油漆了
mix property is being used so when you
MIX属性正在使用 因此当您
use light pressure you'll get more of
使用轻压力 你会得到更多
the secondary color for a misty effect
雾化效果的次要颜色
make this white or a lighter shade I'll
把这个改成白色或浅色 我会
paint a simple Mountain shape
绘制一个简单的山形
let's try there is a broken pallet knife
让我们试试看有一把折断的托盘刀
that gives a nice paint break effect
这会产生很好的油漆破损效果
where the paint sticks to the canvas in
油漆粘在画布上的地方
some places and not in others as with a
一些地方 而不是在其他地方 如
traditional knife you can get more paint
传统小刀你可以得到更多的油漆
brake with a light touch a heavy touch
轻碰刹车 重踩刹车
will cover the texture
将覆盖纹理
more I'll enable preserve Alpha and use
更多 我将启用保留Alpha和使用
varied pressure to add some snow to one
不同的压力来给一场雪加一些雪
side of the mountain shape make
山体一侧的形状使
subsequent overlapping Strokes to easily
后续重叠笔划可轻松完成
control the buildup of the paint this is
控制油漆的堆积 这是
another rgba brush that simulates imposs
另一个模拟Imposs的RGBA笔刷
you can modify the texture options to
您可以将纹理选项修改为
change the texture of this brush in
在中更改此画笔的纹理
particular contrast controls the fractal
特定的对比度控制着分形图
pattern you can play with this property
您可以使用此属性进行操作的模式
alongside choosing different textures to
除了选择不同的纹理来
get a range of
获取一系列
effects the last thing I want to discuss
影响是我最不想讨论的事情
is using the right brush for the job
使用正确的刷子来完成作业
there are so many brushes that can do
有太多的画笔可以做
essentially the same thing there are
本质上是相同的东西 有
probably a hundred brushes you could use
大概有一百把刷子你可以用
to create trees but you have to think
来创造树木 但你必须思考
about what type of trees you want or
关于你想要什么类型的树或者
what kind of style you want for your
您想要什么样的款式？
painting the best way to find the right
绘画是找到真爱的最好方式
brush is to just experiment with
画笔只是用来做实验的
different brushes and take a look at
不同的画笔 看看
what they can do make observations about
他们能做些什么来观察
how the brush looks and feels for
画笔的外观和手感
instance if you find a brush that looks
如果您发现一个画笔看起来像
like it would work well for painting
就像它能很好地用于绘画一样
trees you can save it as a tree brush
树你可以把它保存为树刷
then any time you want to paint trees
然后任何时候你想要画树
use one of your tree brushes it wouldn't
用你的一把树刷 它不会
make sense to use the airbrush to try
使用喷枪尝试是有意义的
and paint leaves when there are brushes
有刷子的时候画树叶
that can do it more quickly and
这样可以更快地完成这项工作
effectively try to get the effect you
有效地尝试获得你的效果
want in just a few Strokes rather than
我只想打几下 而不是
spending all day rendering objects with
一整天都在使用渲染对象
a basic brush as you work with cre more
在使用Cre More时使用基本画笔
and more you're going to start to
更多的你将会开始
discover which brushes are valuable for
找出哪些刷子有价值
your workflow and if you take time to
您的工作流程 如果您花时间
save and categorize them you'll always
保存并对它们进行分类您将始终
have the right brush available when you
在以下情况下可使用合适的刷子
need it that covers the brushes that I
我需要它来盖住我的刷子
consider to be essential for my
我认为这对我的
workflow
工作流程